<?xml version="1.0"?>
<rss version="2.0">
    <channel ttl="3600" language="en-eu">
        <title>Defense - Latest News</title>
        <link>http://news.prlog.org/ind/defense/</link>
        <description>Defense - Latest News (Press Releases) - Read news before it's news</description>
        <item>
            <title>Army Materiel Command (AMC) Releases Annual Publication &quot;Sustaining the Strength of the Nation&quot;</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235573-army-materiel-command-amc-releases-annual-publication-sustaining-the-strength-of-the-nation.html
            </link>
            <description>Interactive digital edition of the Army Materiel Command's &quot;Sustaining the Strength of the
                Nation&quot; can be viewed on your desktop as well as iPad. Videos, photo galleries, and info-graphics
                launch on your desktop or tablet with a simple click.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Government News: Ray Odierno and Wendy Masiello Discuss Issues Facing U.S. Service Branches</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235545-government-news-ray-odierno-and-wendy-masiello-discuss-issues-facing-us-service-branches.html
            </link>
            <description>ExecutiveGov is part of Executive Mosaic's portfolio of media properties and serves its
                executive audience by covering stories focused on federal agencies, U.S. foreign policy and each branch
                of government.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMINT Consulting adds TEAC series modems to elite decoder package</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235045-comint-consulting-adds-teac-series-modems-to-elite-decoder-package.html
            </link>
            <description>Four SIGINT modems offer insight into military communications and intelligence</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CDO Technologies uses CORENA solutions to expand their S1000D and MILSPEC sustainment services
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234799-cdo-technologies-uses-corena-solutions-to-expand-their-s1000d-and-milspec-sustainment-services.html
            </link>
            <description>CORENA, a global leader in S1000D software and implementation services, announced today that
                they have signed a strategic agreement with CDO Technologies, Inc.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>U.S. Army Corps of Engineers Buffalo District to Receive SEBAC's 2012-2013 Award for Excellence
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233724-us-army-corps-of-engineers-buffalo-district-to-receive-sebacs-2012-2013-award-for-excellence.html
            </link>
            <description>The Small Environmental Business Action Coalition, Inc. and PilieroMazza PLLC are pleased to
                announce the recipient of the Award for Excellence in Awarding Small Business Prime Contracts.  This
                year’s recipient is the U.S.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Counter-Terrorism Conference Geared for Success</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12232971-counter-terrorism-conference-geared-for-success.html</link>
            <description>Strengthening Dialogue and Cross-Training in C4ISR Disciplines with ITTA Members</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Online Knife Emporium KnivesFor.Me is Open for Business</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233012-online-knife-emporium-knivesforme-is-open-for-business.html</link>
            <description>A brand new online shop KnivesFor.Me has launched with an extensive stock of knives and knife
                accessories including hunting knives, pocket knives, automatic knives, throwing knives, concealable
                knives, and others.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Executives from the Aerospace and Defense Industries to Meet at the ITAR Compliance WEST Conference
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12231925-executives-from-the-aerospace-and-defense-industries-to-meet-at-the-itar-compliance-west-conference.html
            </link>
            <description>Navigating the Complexities of the Changing Compliance Structure through Improved Operational
                Communication, Language Interpretation and Jurisdictional Understanding
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>U.S. Aerospace And Defense Suppliers To Meet Asia-Pacific Buyers, Partners At Seoul ADEX Show</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12231475-us-aerospace-and-defense-suppliers-to-meet-asia-pacific-buyers-partners-at-seoul-adex-show.html
            </link>
            <description>U.S. company experts will share news and knowledge face-to-face with the region’s aerospace and
                defense community
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Power Ten, Inc. to be at NDIA's Expeditionary Warfare Conference</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12231458-power-ten-inc-to-be-at-ndias-expeditionary-warfare-conference.html
            </link>
            <description>Tony White, Director of Sales &amp; Marketing, New Technologies, will be on-hand at this year’s
                EWC event and available to meet with you and answer any questions about the Power Ten, Inc. and our
                services.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Power Ten, Inc. adds Hungry Giant product to its Environmental line</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12231411-power-ten-inc-adds-hungry-giant-product-to-its-environmental-line.html
            </link>
            <description>The defense centric company has signed a deal with California-based Organics Waste Recycling to
                be the exclusive sales agent for their Hungry Giant line of food waste dehydrators to the United States
                Department of Defense.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>S4 Announces Corporate Promotions, Reorganization</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12229999-s4-announces-corporate-promotions-reorganization.html</link>
            <description>Burlington, MA - S4 Inc., a professional services and consulting firm catering to US Government
                and DoD customers, announced several promotions as part of a reorganization of the company. These
                internal changes are effective today.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMINT Consulting Showcases Premiere SIGINT/COMINT Decoder at October AOC Convention</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12230009-comint-consulting-showcases-premiere-sigintcomint-decoder-at-october-aoc-convention.html
            </link>
            <description>COMINT Consulting, member of the Association of Old Crows (AOC), will attend the AOC ‘s 50th
                annual international Symposium and Convention in Washington, D.C. from October 27-30.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Executive Profiles at SAS Federal and Level 3 Communications</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12229381-executive-profiles-at-sas-federal-and-level-3-communications.html</link>
            <description>GovCon Executive is a leader in providing news, profiles and timely updates on some of the most
                powerful leaders in government contracting.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dreamer, Military Fiction at Its Best - Good Weekend Read - Free Today</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12228533-dreamer-military-fiction-at-its-best-good-weekend-read-free-today.html
            </link>
            <description>Attorney Phil Davidson, Author, Vietnam Veteran, PTSD and SWAT Law Enforcement Expert Dreamer -
                Novel free today on Amazon Vietnam Veteran Phil Davidson's life reads like a spy novel, full of
                intrigue, mystery, combat and even a happy ending.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ampex announces its fastest, most advanced network file server ever: the TuffServ® 640</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227284-ampex-announces-its-fastest-most-advanced-network-file-server-ever-the-tuffserv-640.html
            </link>
            <description>Ampex’s ultra-wideband network file server/recorder boasts lightning-fast write speeds of up to
                1GB/second, 10 GigE connectivity – and more than 12TB of hot-swappable storage.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Joseph Federico and NJ MET Announce the Publication of Electrical Testing Article on RF Globalnet
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12228305-joseph-federico-and-nj-met-announce-the-publication-of-electrical-testing-article-on-rf-globalnet.html
            </link>
            <description>NJ MET announced that Joseph Federico’s article “Counterfeit Component Detection Through
                Electrical Testing” has been published by RF Globalnet on its website. The article is the featured
                article in the October 8th RF Globalnet newsletter.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>White Mountain Tactical Introduces Protex Firearm Lubricants &amp; Protectant</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227331-white-mountain-tactical-introduces-protex-firearm-lubricants-protectant.html
            </link>
            <description>New Protex Firearm Lubricants and Protectants offer superior protection and high performance
                boundary lubrication in any environmental or high demand condition.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Business News: Executive Moves at Serco, Fluor, CH2M Hill, Ball Aerospace and Northrop</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227875-business-news-executive-moves-at-serco-fluor-ch2m-hill-ball-aerospace-and-northrop.html
            </link>
            <description>Executive Mosaic’s weekly round-up of news is a can’t-miss, digestible snapshot of the GovCon
                industry covering the biggest executive moves, mergers &amp;amp; acquisitions and contracts straight
                from the pen of one of GovCon’s most respected...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Century Fasteners Corp. and Cherry Aerospace at NIFMS Expo</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12227669-century-fasteners-corp-and-cherry-aerospace-at-nifms-expo.html</link>
            <description>Century Fasteners Corp. and Cherry Aerospace Relationship Showcased at National Industrial
                Fastener &amp; Mill Expo, Las Vegas, NV
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>CEA to showcase innovative CBRN-E solutions at TRANSEC 2013</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12227720-cea-to-showcase-innovative-cbrn-solutions-at-transec-2013.html</link>
            <description>CEA, the French Alternative Energies and Atomic Energy Commission, will exhibit its innovative
                CBRN-E prevention solutions – for dealing with chemical, biological, radiological and nuclear risks, as
                well as explosives-related threats – at TRANSEC
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMINT Consulting Announces Fall Test Drive of Premiere SIGINT/COMINT Decoder</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227699-comint-consulting-announces-fall-test-drive-of-premiere-sigintcomint-decoder.html
            </link>
            <description>Krypto500 demonstrations available at AUSA Exposition, October 21-23</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RT LTA Systems LTD to participate in AUSA 2013 annual meeting and exposition</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227695-rt-lta-systems-ltd-to-participate-in-ausa-2013-annual-meeting-and-exposition.html
            </link>
            <description>RT LTA Systems LTD will exhibit at the AUSA 2013 annual meeting and exposition for the first
                time. Held in the Walter E. Washington Convention Center, Washington, D.C. RT LTA Systems LTD will take
                part of the Israeli Pavilion hall B, booth 2452
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>GKG Group celebrated its Founder’s Day on 13th October</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12227481-gkg-group-celebrated-its-founders-day-on-13th-october.html</link>
            <description>On Sunday, 13th October, 2013, GKG Group celebrated its Founder’s Day, marking the birth
                anniversary of Mr. G K Gupta the founder of GKG Group.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Global Commercial Aircraft Landing Gears Market Size And Share 2012 - 2016</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227462-global-commercial-aircraft-landing-gears-market-size-and-share-2012-2016.html
            </link>
            <description>ResearchMoz include new market research report&quot; Global Commercial Aircraft Landing Gears
                Market Industry Analysis, Growth, Trends And Forecast &quot; to its huge collection of research reports.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dynetics Modular Instrumentation System on Display at Las Vegas Conference</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12227274-dynetics-modular-instrumentation-system-on-display-at-las-vegas-conference.html
            </link>
            <description>International Telemetering Conference is October 21-24, 2013</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>News of the Week: Bill Bodie Joins Fluor as SVP of BD</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12227169-news-of-the-week-bill-bodie-joins-fluor-as-svp-of-bd.html</link>
            <description>GovCon Wire publishes a number of stories each week that includes executive appointments, M&amp;amp;A
                activity and earnings reports at GovCon firms.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cassidian wins contract to extend Asia’s largest TETRA network in Beijing</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226944-cassidian-wins-contract-to-extend-asias-largest-tetra-network-in-beijing.html
            </link>
            <description>Cassidian will provide two DXT3 TETRA switches and over 100 TETRA base stations. Secure radio
                communications, extensive coverage and excellent reliability now for up to 110,000 users from different
                government agencies
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Government News: Senate Tries to End Shutdown, Air Force Not Ready for Audit</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226562-government-news-senate-tries-to-end-shutdown-air-force-not-ready-for-audit.html
            </link>
            <description>ExecutiveGov is part of Executive Mosaic's portfolio of media properties and serves its
                executive audience by covering stories focused on federal agencies, U.S. foreign policy and each branch
                of government.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Patricia Davis, former Assistant Director, USDOJ Civil Division, joins GeyerGorey LLP</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226202-patricia-davis-former-assistant-director-usdoj-civil-division-joins-geyergorey-llp.html
            </link>
            <description>Patricia Davis, a twenty-year veteran of the Department of Justice, has joined GeyerGorey LLP
                as of counsel. She previously served as Assistant Director, Fraud Section, Civil Division, U.S.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMINT Consulting Upgrades to Create the Most Advanced Decoder in the COMINT/SIGINT Industry</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225910-comint-consulting-upgrades-to-create-the-most-advanced-decoder-in-the-comintsigint-industry.html
            </link>
            <description>COMINT/SIGINT experts add more power to their decoding software</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Executive Profiles of Leaders from Microsoft and Booz Allen</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12225857-executive-profiles-of-leaders-from-microsoft-and-booz-allen.html</link>
            <description>GovCon Executive is a leader in providing news, profiles and timely updates on some of the most
                powerful leaders in government contracting.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>TMA Honors Collard Among 31 Founding Members at 25th Annual Conference</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225203-tma-honors-collard-among-31-founding-members-at-25th-annual-conference.html
            </link>
            <description>Turnaround Management Association honors Collard Among 31 Founding Members of the
                Association.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>AUSA and RMS Productions Announce Unprecedented Partnership to Tell Army Story at Unit Level</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12223758-ausa-and-rms-productions-announce-unprecedented-partnership-to-tell-army-story-at-unit-level.html
            </link>
            <description>“Remember My Service” recognition program to affect all Active, Guard, and Reserve Soldiers;
                Private sector invited to support; Communication platform for families to better understand Soldiers’
                service
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>HAC Expands Efforts to Create Affordable Housing for Rural Veterans</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12224789-hac-expands-efforts-to-create-affordable-housing-for-rural-veterans.html
            </link>
            <description>HAC Begins Second Year of Affordable Housing for Rural Veterans Program thanks to a Second
                Round of Funding The Home Depot Foundation
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>COMINT Consulting collaborates with Ettus Research</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12224421-comint-consulting-collaborates-with-ettus-research.html</link>
            <description>COMINT Consulting, a leader in communications and signal intelligence (COMINT/SIGINT)
                solutions, recently added the power of their elite decoder, the Krypto500, to the Ettus Research USRP
                (Universal Software Radio Peripheral) and software defined radio...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Women's Streets Safety Seminar</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12222815-womens-streets-safety-seminar.html</link>
            <description>Women's Street Safe Seminar It's getting close to Halloween and the last thing you want to
                worry about is your safety while Trick or Treating with your children or going to a party.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Government News: More Gov't Workers to be put on Furlough</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12222935-government-news-more-govt-workers-to-be-put-on-furlough.html</link>
            <description>ExecutiveGov is part of Executive Mosaic's portfolio of media properties and serves its
                executive audience by covering stories focused on federal agencies, U.S. foreign policy and each branch
                of government.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Joseph Federico, Director of NJ MET Inc., Honors Genoveva Valentin for 25 Years of Service</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12222371-joseph-federico-director-of-nj-met-inc-honors-genoveva-valentin-for-25-years-of-service.html
            </link>
            <description>NJ MET celebrated Genoveva Valentin’s 25th service anniversary at a luncheon in her honor.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Executive Profiles of Leaders from Cubic Corp. and Northrop Grumman</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12222268-executive-profiles-of-leaders-from-cubic-corp-and-northrop-grumman.html
            </link>
            <description>GovCon Executive is a leader in providing news, profiles and timely updates on some of the most
                powerful leaders in government contracting.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Aviation Search Group Names Jason Zelenak Sales Manager</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12220887-aviation-search-group-names-jason-zelenak-sales-manager.html</link>
            <description>Aviation Search Group, an executive style, direct-placement search firm dedicated to the
                aviation and aerospace industries, announced the promotion of Jason Zelenak to Sales Manager.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ADL Embedded Solutions Announces ADLQM87PC - 4th Gen Intel Core i7 SBC</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12220671-adl-embedded-solutions-announces-adlqm87pc-4th-gen-intel-core-i7-sbc.html
            </link>
            <description>ADL Embedded Solutions, a leading provider of customizable, high-performance embedded solutions
                for demanding thermal and rugged environments, announces availability of its ADLQM87PC PCIe/104 SBC
                based on the 4th generation Intel® Core™ processor.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Government News: DoD Awards Contracts Despite Shutdown and NASA Asks for Commercial R&amp;D
                Partners
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12220076-government-news-dod-awards-contracts-despite-shutdown-and-nasa-asks-for-commercial-rd-partners.html
            </link>
            <description>ExecutiveGov is part of Executive Mosaic's portfolio of media properties and serves its
                executive audience by covering stories focused on federal agencies, U.S. foreign policy and each branch
                of government.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Military Flight Planning website goes viral</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12219694-military-flight-planning-website-goes-viral.html</link>
            <description>New website receives hundreds of requests for accounts in few hours of release as link goes
                viral.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Border Security: Intelligent solutions to better enhance</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12219820-border-security-intelligent-solutions-to-better-enhance.html</link>
            <description>SMi Group reports: Industry leading experts in Border Security will meet in Sofia in February
                2014
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Precision Aviation Group (PAG) expands use of the Pentagon 2000SQL™ System</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12219495-precision-aviation-group-pag-expands-use-of-the-pentagon-2000sql-system.html
            </link>
            <description>Additional companies added seamlessly under existing single database.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>News of the Week: Michael Maiorana Named Verizon Public Sector Lead</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12219458-news-of-the-week-michael-maiorana-named-verizon-public-sector-lead.html
            </link>
            <description>GovCon Wire publishes a number of stories each week that includes executive appointments, M&amp;amp;A
                activity and earnings reports at GovCon firms.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>LTG David Valcourt (Ret.) Joins the R2 Associates Board of Advisors</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12218703-ltg-david-valcourt-ret-joins-the-r2-associates-board-of-advisors.html
            </link>
            <description>Morristown, NJ, October 1, 2013, – Today, R2 Associates, LLC, announced that LTG David Valcourt
                (Ret.) has joined the firm’s Board of Advisors.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Texas VFW Announces Support for Honor Our Soldiers Campaign</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12218681-texas-vfw-announces-support-for-honor-our-soldiers-campaign.html</link>
            <description>The Texas VFW supports the national Honor Our Soldiers campaign to pay tribute to American
                veterans, past and present.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Government News: Robert Hale and Tim Kaine on Possible Gov't Shutdown</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12218664-government-news-robert-hale-and-tim-kaine-on-possible-govt-shutdown.html
            </link>
            <description>ExecutiveGov is part of Executive Mosaic's portfolio of media properties and serves its
                executive audience by covering stories focused on federal agencies, U.S. foreign policy and each branch
                of government.
            </description>
        </item>
    </channel>
    <channel ttl="3600" language="en-eu">
        <title>Computers - Latest News</title>
        <link>http://news.prlog.org/ind/computers/</link>
        <description>Computers - Latest News (Press Releases) - Read news before it's news</description>
        <item>
            <title>WebMedicPro &amp; Sundance System form Strategic Partnership</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235590-webmedicpro-sundance-system-form-strategic-partnership.html</link>
            <description>WebMedicPro has formed a Strategic Partnership with Sundance System to better serve the EMS
                industry with integrated CAD and ePCR
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>St. Louis Area IT Training Company Offers New Microsoft Office 2013 Classes</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235587-st-louis-area-it-training-company-offers-new-microsoft-office-2013-classes.html
            </link>
            <description>St. Louis (MO)— ONLC Training Centers now has courses available for Microsoft Office 2013.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>TruePath Technologies has Now Joined FISPA to Deliver Highly Competitive Services</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235546-truepath-technologies-has-now-joined-fispa-to-deliver-highly-competitive-services.html
            </link>
            <description>The consulting services and software offered by TruePath help companies improve network
                potential
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ashwin Srivastava joins Tech Anipr as its CEO</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235443-ashwin-srivastava-joins-tech-anipr-as-its-ceo.html</link>
            <description>Ashwin Srivastava, co-founder of Incept, and a successful serial entrepreneur, has joined the
                board of Tech Anipr, an upcoming Software Lab company, and incubated at IIIT Hyderabad
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>L-Tron Earns Global Recognition with Award from Advantech</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233790-tron-earns-global-recognition-with-award-from-advantech.html</link>
            <description>L-Tron receives &quot;Best Growth&quot; award from Advantech at 2013 World Partner Conference
                in Dubai.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Riaxe Launches ‘Thin Admin’ Responsive Design Template</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235331-riaxe-launches-thin-admin-responsive-design-template.html</link>
            <description>Riaxe is elated to announce that a new template developed from scratch has been launched on
                themeforest.net. The template is known as ‘Thin Admin’template. It is based on the Bootstrap 3
                Framework. The project took 20 days to complete.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>YRCG Launches Weblink 1.4 best browser by students company on earth</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235329-yrcg-launches-weblink-14-best-browser-by-students-company-on-earth.html
            </link>
            <description>YRCG ready to attract mass of users for its new update. With the release of WEblink 1.4 YRCG is
                ready to create a revolution for browsers
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MailEnable Offers Complete Email Solutions for Small Businesses</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235306-mailenable-offers-complete-email-solutions-for-small-businesses.html
            </link>
            <description>Small businesses often turn to mail server software to offer the collaboration and messaging
                services the company needs to succeed in today’s global marketplace.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SAMSA President Presents Papers at 50th Annual Meeting of Missouri Valley Economics Association
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235294-samsa-president-presents-papers-at-50th-annual-meeting-of-missouri-valley-economics-association.html
            </link>
            <description>Saginaw, Michigan, October 22, 2013 – SAMSA President Mike Stackhouse was included on the
                program at the 50th Annual meeting of the Missouri Valley Economics Association in Kansas City, MO.
                &amp;nbsp;The meeting was October 17 – 19, and Mr.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Castlegem launching Intel E5 v2 servers</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235258-castlegem-launching-intel-e5-v2-servers.html</link>
            <description>We are happy to announce the official release of the E5-v2 series for our dedicated server
                range. We will still be offering the v1 ones of course, servers that have achieved excellent uptime and
                performance already.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Rhys Darby Voices Kids' iPad Book App for Yoozoo Books</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235207-rhys-darby-voices-kids-ipad-book-app-for-yoozoo-books.html</link>
            <description>October 24, 2013 Auckland, New Zealand - Yoozoo Books, a new children's book app publisher,
                today is thrilled to announce the release of Have You Heard, a children's story book and game app for
                iPad.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Mark Mathews Joins tech4SMB Advisory Board</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235197-mark-mathews-joins-tech4smb-advisory-board.html</link>
            <description>Mark Mathews (former President and CEO, Toshiba America Business Solutions) joins innovative
                tech startup tech4SMB Advisory Board
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>The Motorola MC40 Mobile Computer Delivers the Ultimate Customer Service Experience for Retailers
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235163-the-motorola-mc40-mobile-computer-delivers-the-ultimate-customer-service-experience-for-retailers.html
            </link>
            <description>Melbourne October, 2013 – Introducing The Motorola MC40 the easy way to deliver better customer
                services that will impress today's demanding and technology savvy customers.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Website builder adds Social Media</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235118-website-builder-adds-social-media.html</link>
            <description>Reason8 today announced the launch of social media pack for their award winning self-build
                website service.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SIMBA Food Traceability Software Tracks More Than Lots and is PTI Compliant</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235123-simba-food-traceability-software-tracks-more-than-lots-and-is-pti-compliant.html
            </link>
            <description>REDMOND - WA – October 31, 2013 - Dynamic Systems, Inc., a leading software developer
                specializing in barcode data collection has announced the release of SIMBA Lite , designed to provide
                cold storage The ability to process &amp; label ll products.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Equipment Tracking Software Adds 2D Dot Label &amp; Improves Efficiency and Safety for Fire
                Departments
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235102-equipment-tracking-software-adds-2d-dot-label-improves-efficiency-and-safety-for-fire-departments.html
            </link>
            <description>Redmond, Washington / October 30, 2013 / Dynamic Systems, Inc., a leader in Barcode Tracking
                Systems, has announced a new 2 Dimensional label to be used with The Checkmate Equipment and Toolroom
                for Fire and EMS Departments.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Protection and Licensing Tools Enhanced for QuickLicense 7, Windows 8.1 and Mavericks</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234940-protection-and-licensing-tools-enhanced-for-quicklicense-7-windows-81-and-mavericks.html
            </link>
            <description>New QuickLicense Server, QLRT Xcode, DocProtect, PluginFMQLRT and PluginXojoQLRT Releases
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Italy hosted Software Testers for CITCON OpenSpace Event</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234910-italy-hosted-software-testers-for-citcon-openspace-event.html</link>
            <description>CITCON event was held in Turin, Italy, the 27th -28th of &amp;nbsp;September 2013 CITCON is an
                OpenSpace event that was held in Talent Garden Torino.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New email security cloud service launched by Novak Networx LLC of Janesville WI</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234889-new-email-security-cloud-service-launched-by-novak-networx-llc-of-janesville-wi.html
            </link>
            <description>A new cloud based email security service for small businesses has launched from startup Novak
                Networx, who was the first tenant in the newly built Janesville Innovation Center.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Maintain long-term control of your network thanks to smart discovery and rule-based monitoring
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234040-maintain-long-term-control-of-your-network-thanks-to-smart-discovery-and-rule-based-monitoring.html
            </link>
            <description>Stop slipping back into configuration nightmares. The newly released NetCrunch 7.3 eases not
                only your initial monitoring setup but assists you in keeping order when you add new devices,
                technologies and targets to your monitoring.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Amigabit Offered Data Recovery Utility at half Price in 2013 Halloween Promotion</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234687-amigabit-offered-data-recovery-utility-at-half-price-in-2013-halloween-promotion.html
            </link>
            <description>The 2013 Halloween holiday is just around the corner, Amigabit, a professional computer
                maintenance and data recovery software developer, has been holding the 2013 Halloween Promotion for
                weeks.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Barcode Tracking Software Solution for Food Processors with Unique Features</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234468-barcode-tracking-software-solution-for-food-processors-with-unique-features.html
            </link>
            <description>October 28, 2013 / Redmond, Washington/ Dynamic Systems, Inc., a leader in barcode Tracking
                Solutions since 1981, has announced the launch of an affordable software suite for small to mid-sized
                food processors.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Metal Tags Help Companies Track Equipment</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234461-metal-tags-help-companies-track-equipment.html</link>
            <description>Redmond, Washington October 25, 2013/ Dynamic Systems, Inc., a leader in mobile data collection
                applications, has introduced Metal Barcode Tags to the Checkmate Tool &amp; Equipment Software offering.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Automatic Removal Solution to Delete CryptoLocker Ransomware Virus Posted on PC Fix Site</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234446-automatic-removal-solution-to-delete-cryptolocker-ransomware-virus-posted-on-pc-fix-site.html
            </link>
            <description>Computer users are now finding refuge in knowing that they can automatically remove the
                stubborn and annoying CryptoLocker Ransomware virus from their computer through resources on an Online
                Safety site removal guide.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Portrait Professional 11 “Highly Commended” in GOTY awards by Digital Photo and Practical Phot
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234340-portrait-professional-11-highly-commended-in-goty-awards-by-digital-photo-and-practical-phot.html
            </link>
            <description>Anthropics’ Portrait Professional 11, easy-to-use photo editing software, wins the Highly
                Commended status in the Best Software category in The Gear of the Year 2013 Awards by Digital Photo and
                Practical Photography magazines, UK.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>LymTal International ERP Project Upgrade</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234298-lymtal-international-erp-project-upgrade.html</link>
            <description>LymTal International Inc designated USATInc to upgrade their Enterprise Resource Planning
                software ‘Great Plains’ also known in the industry as ‘Microsoft Dynamics’.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>West Trax Saves Costs for SAP ® HCM Analytics Users</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234285-west-trax-saves-costs-for-sap-hcm-analytics-users.html</link>
            <description>SAP ® optimisation through transparency – Now for HR. Years of successfully optimising SAP®
                value for clients prompted West Trax to expand its portfolio with a solution which specifically
                addresses HCM issues.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>My Lockbox 3: Free Protection of Private Files. Now with Instant Password Recovery</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234017-my-lockbox-3-free-protection-of-private-files-now-with-instant-password-recovery.html
            </link>
            <description>FSPro Labs announces the release of My Lockbox 3, a new version of its software to protect
                files and folders on local hard disk of Windows PC.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MPDS4 REVIEW 1.2 Release: 3D Review Tool for Industrial Plants and Data</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233989-mpds4-review-12-release-3d-review-tool-for-industrial-plants-and-data.html
            </link>
            <description>The new version of CAD Schroer’s external 3D review tool for MPDS4 and MEDUSA4 data makes it
                even easier for industrial designers to communicate ideas and changes to project stakeholders and
                customers
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Samsung Monitors Win Three SEAD Global Awards 2013</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233955-samsung-monitors-win-three-sead-global-awards-2013.html</link>
            <description>Samsung wins Best Medium-sized Monitor, Best Large-sized Monitor and Best Emerging Technology
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Expert-Team Provides Enterprise Internet Monitoring Solutions</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233947-expert-team-provides-enterprise-internet-monitoring-solutions.html
            </link>
            <description>Do you know what your employees are doing in front of their company PC? Many employers believe
                that their staffs are spending time wisely in front of their work desk PC. “We expect them to work on
                job related matters when using their PC.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Ozeki Announces 3D VoIP Video Calling Technology</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233941-ozeki-announces-3d-voip-video-calling-technology.html</link>
            <description>Ozeki today introduced a revolutionary technology that makes live 3D video calls possible. The
                new technology has the potential to transform visual industries such as sport broadcasting, product
                shows, on-line conferencing and many others.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Lattitude Solutions Web Design | Houston Web Design</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233894-lattitude-solutions-web-design-houston-web-design.html</link>
            <description>Lattitude Solutions Web Design is pleased to announce its 2nd location in Houston, TX. The new
                office is located in Pearland, TX and will focus exclusively on web design and graphic design in
                Houston, TX area.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Crowdfunding Campaign for New I.T. Book Series</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233849-crowdfunding-campaign-for-new-it-book-series.html</link>
            <description>Indiegogo Crowdfunding Campaign Launch for New I.T. Book Series</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>United EMS a Puerto Rican EMS agency goes paperless using mobile ePCR</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233687-united-ems-puerto-rican-ems-agency-goes-paperless-using-mobile-epcr.html
            </link>
            <description>WebMedicPro's mobile ePCR is chosen by the Puerto Rican EMS agency United EMS</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>InfoStream Inc is growing its team</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233569-infostream-inc-is-growing-its-team.html</link>
            <description>InfoStream Inc, one of the leading IT provider in the Palm Beach area, are expanding and
                looking for their next super star.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Gigastrand stays committed to OS development.</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12232071-gigastrand-stays-committed-to-os-development.html</link>
            <description>Despite slow fundraising efforts on Indiegogo, Gigastrand says it is committed to developing
                it's own OS to 1.0.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dr. Lettsome Chimes in on the Website Problems of Healthcare.gov</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233459-dr-lettsome-chimes-in-on-the-website-problems-of-healthcaregov.html
            </link>
            <description>In the newest opinion column written by Dr. Clyde A. Lettsome, he gives insight into who is
                really to blame for the development problems with www.Healthcare.gov .
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Atlantic Inkjet brings the most Chilling Discounts on Refill Kits &amp; Compatible Cartridges</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233403-atlantic-inkjet-brings-the-most-chilling-discounts-on-refill-kits-compatible-cartridges.html
            </link>
            <description>Irwindale, California 29 October 2013 Atlantic Inkjet, a decade old name in the printing
                solution industry, has introduced a festive discount offer at its online store.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MEDIA ALERT-FASETTO Presents Technical Paper and Demos Industry Leading File Sharing Solution at
                Clo
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232414-media-alert-fasetto-presents-technical-paper-and-demos-industry-leading-file-sharing-solution-at-clo.html
            </link>
            <description>Unique Ground Breaking Technology Enable File Sharing Across Any Device</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Automation Suite for VMware now supports vCenter 5.5, ESXi 5.5, Workstation 10 and Fusion 6</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233120-automation-suite-for-vmware-now-supports-vcenter-55-esxi-55-workstation-10-and-fusion-6.html
            </link>
            <description>F.W.Roller &amp; Associates LLC, cross-platform business software developers and Enterprise
                Resource Planning consultants, today announced availability of Automation Suite 2013 Release 5 for
                VMware, which includes vmCLIpboard, vmProcessStrobe and...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Toughshield appoints country managers for France and Italy</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233287-toughshield-appoints-country-managers-for-france-and-italy.html</link>
            <description>Arnaud Fessard and Giuseppe Luchesa appointed as country managers and Patrice Deniau as
                pre-sales engineer as Toughshield expands its sales operations in Southern Europe and North Africa
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Advanced Color Swatches Magento Extension with Multi Zoom Launched by M-Connect Media</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233215-advanced-color-swatches-magento-extension-with-multi-zoom-launched-by-connect-media.html
            </link>
            <description>M-Connect Media, the online store for getting a myriad range of Magento Commerce solutions has
                launched the Advanced Color Swatches Extension with Multi Zoom.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dropmyemail values your privacy</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12233187-dropmyemail-values-your-privacy.html</link>
            <description>In light of recent revelations about NSA’s incessant and indiscriminate screening of
                everybody’s emails – we at Dropmyemail would like to reassure you of the safety and complete privacy of
                your emails.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Advantech and InduSoft Join Together</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12232985-advantech-and-indusoft-join-together.html</link>
            <description>Advantech and InduSoft Join Together to Provide Large Screen Multi-Touch Panel PCs with
                InduSoft’s Latest HMI Software
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New High-Quality Model 9458 4-Channel A/B/Offline Switch Offers Lifetime Guarantee</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232921-new-high-quality-model-9458-4-channel-aboffline-switch-offers-lifetime-guarantee.html
            </link>
            <description>The Model 9458 RJ45 CAT5e A/B/Offline switch packs 4 channels of A/B/Offline switching
                capability into a slim rackmount enclosure.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SoftNAS Announces Sale of SoftNAS Essentials</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12232769-softnas-announces-sale-of-softnas-essentials.html</link>
            <description>Targets small and home offices as well as individual end users</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Entagy launches version 3.0 of its online project management software solution, &quot;happytodos&quot;</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232759-entagy-launches-version-30-of-its-online-project-management-software-solution-happytodos.html
            </link>
            <description>Entagy Internet Solutions, Ltd, the software development firm have announced the launch of the
                3rd version of their popular project management software tool which is due out this November.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Spotlite Radio Presents Daniel Jones</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12232734-spotlite-radio-presents-daniel-jones.html</link>
            <description>Spotlite Radio Presents Owner of PC Expressions LLC, Daniel Jones</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>dataglobal Forms Partnership with DocuLynx to Expand presence in the US Market</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232682-dataglobal-forms-partnership-with-doculynx-to-expand-presence-in-the-us-market.html
            </link>
            <description>DocuLynx to offer dataglobal information governance solutions, which use data classification,
                and archiving, and enterprise search to identify, categorize, retain, and search for information for
                compliance and legal purposes.
            </description>
        </item>
    </channel>
    <channel ttl="3600" language="en-eu">
        <title>Biotech - Latest News</title>
        <link>http://news.prlog.org/ind/biotech/</link>
        <description>Biotech - Latest News (Press Releases) - Read news before it's news</description>
        <item>
            <title>Heart And Vascular Outcomes Research Institute Launches</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235543-heart-and-vascular-outcomes-research-institute-launches.html</link>
            <description>The first-of-its-kind Venous Patient Outcome Registry gives patients instant access to
                treatment outcomes.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Broadleaf Capital Partners To Conduct Conference Call</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12235523-broadleaf-capital-partners-to-conduct-conference-call.html</link>
            <description>Broadleaf Capital Partners, Inc. (OTC:BDLF) will conduct a conference call on Wednesday,
                November 6, 2013 at 10:00 AM pacific time.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Grifols Promotes Quality Systems</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234784-grifols-promotes-quality-systems.html</link>
            <description>Grifols, a global healthcare company based in Barcelona Spain, has begun construction on a
                “showcase” Control Room at their facility in Clayton North Carolina, that employs over 2000 people.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Andrew Maas to speak on inTBIR at the 4th Annual Traumatic Brain Injury Conference</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235485-andrew-maas-to-speak-on-intbir-at-the-4th-annual-traumatic-brain-injury-conference.html
            </link>
            <description>The 4th Annual Traumatic Brain Injury is pleased to announce that Andrew Maas, MD, Ph.D.,
                Professor and Chairman at Antwerp University Hospital and University of Antwerp will return for the 2014
                conference.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>NAMSR News: Medtronic CoreValve U.S. Pivotal Trial results reveal positive outcomes for patients
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12235403-namsr-news-medtronic-corevalve-us-pivotal-trial-results-reveal-positive-outcomes-for-patients.html
            </link>
            <description>Medtronic, Inc. (NYSE: MDT) has announced the highly anticipated results from the CoreValve
                U.S. Pivotal Trial, the first U.S. data presented on the Medtronic CoreValve® System.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BPS Bioscience, Inc. Introduces New Tools and Services to Accelerate PD-1/PD-L Research</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234968-bps-bioscience-inc-introduces-new-tools-and-services-to-accelerate-pd-1pd-research.html
            </link>
            <description>Unique Portfolio of Proteins and Assay Kits for PD-1-related Research and Drug Discovery
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MOgene LC Announces the Addition of Illumina HiSeq</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12234385-mogene-lc-announces-the-addition-of-illumina-hiseq.html</link>
            <description>MOgene LC, a full service genomics service provider, announces the addition of Illumina HiSeq
                to further expand its offerings.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kingfisher Biotech’s Chicken IL-21 Protein Activity Confirmed by an Independent Lab</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234369-kingfisher-biotechs-chicken-il-21-protein-activity-confirmed-by-an-independent-lab.html
            </link>
            <description>IL-21 is a member of the type I cytokine family. Other members of the family include IL-2 and
                IL-15. IL-21 signals through the common gamma-chain and a unique IL-21 receptor.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tecan’s AC Extraction Plate™ provides a unique sample preparation tool for LC-MS</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12234183-tecans-ac-extraction-plate-provides-unique-sample-preparation-tool-for-lc-ms.html
            </link>
            <description>Tecan’s newly launched AC Extraction Plate is a revolutionary, automation-friendly solution
                designed to streamline sample preparation for LC-MS analysis of small molecules.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pharos Anounces New Clincial Trials For Wireless Breast Tumor Marker Technology</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12233499-pharos-anounces-new-clincial-trials-for-wireless-breast-tumor-marker-technology.html
            </link>
            <description>Pharos breast tumor marker technology will enable more effective breast cancer surgery
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Intuitive Surgical Claims More Than 50% Savings Using Open Source EDC ClinCapture</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232939-intuitive-surgical-claims-more-than-50-savings-using-open-source-edc-clincapture.html
            </link>
            <description>Clinical Data Manager Mark Burns Explains How Intuitive Surgical Deployed Clinovo’s Open Source
                EDC System ClinCapture for Over 15 Studies
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Quincy Bioscience Launches New National Advertisement in USA Today</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232932-quincy-bioscience-launches-new-national-advertisement-in-usa-today.html
            </link>
            <description>Makers of Prevagen, best-selling memory supplement, announce national ad campaign</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Kingfisher Biotech’s Mouse GM-CSF Protein Found to be 40% More Active</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232719-kingfisher-biotechs-mouse-gm-csf-protein-found-to-be-40-more-active.html
            </link>
            <description>Independent testing laboratory verifies that Kingfisher Biotech's Mouse GM-CSF is 40% more
                active than another commercially available Mouse GM-CSF protein. These proteins are routinely used in
                cell culture.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BBI Solutions is launching new assay sensitivity enhancing technologies at Medica 2013</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232665-bbi-solutions-is-launching-new-assay-sensitivity-enhancing-technologies-at-medica-2013.html
            </link>
            <description>New and unique sensitivity enhancing technology for assay development will be launched by BBI
                Solutions at Medica 2013, alongside detailed information on its portfolio of critical reagents and
                contract manufacturing services.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Zaiput Flow Technologies awards $10,000 in grants to three leading flow chemistry groups</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12232102-zaiput-flow-technologies-awards-10000-in-grants-to-three-leading-flow-chemistry-groups.html
            </link>
            <description>Zaiput Flow Technologies, an MIT spin off marketing innovative devices for continuous flow
                chemistry, awards $10,000 in grants to 3 of the most prominent flow chemistry research groups worldwide.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Abaxis and LamdaGen Corporation Enter Into R&amp;D Diagnostic Collaboration</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12231873-abaxis-and-lamdagen-corporation-enter-into-rd-diagnostic-collaboration.html
            </link>
            <description>UNION CITY AND MENLO PARK, CA, Abaxis, Inc. (NasdaqGS: ABAX), a medical products company
                manufacturing point-of-care blood instrumentation and consumables to the medical, research and
                veterinary markets, and privately-held LamdaGen Corporation, an...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Australian Approval for Dismate PE, The new Technology For Indian Meal Moth Management</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12231264-australian-approval-for-dismate-pe-the-new-technology-for-indian-meal-moth-management.html
            </link>
            <description>Dismate PE achieves Australian approval to start field testing . The product is already
                commercially available in United stated and the European union providing a reliable control of Indian
                meal Moth in food processing and storage facilities.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Training the Future Biomanufacturing Workforce</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12231325-training-the-future-biomanufacturing-workforce.html</link>
            <description>Industry-Academia Partnerships Are Highlighted in a Roundtable Discussion</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>DDC Increases the Identification Power of its DNA Tests by More Than 500%</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12231155-ddc-increases-the-identification-power-of-its-dna-tests-by-more-than-500.html
            </link>
            <description>DDC (DNA Diagnostics Centre) and it’s division, DDC Medical, will now examine 22 genetic
                markers versus 17, which until today has been the core standard in the industry
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Looking for Life on Mars… and other places</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12230866-looking-for-life-on-mars-and-other-places.html</link>
            <description>On Monday, November 18th, Crowell Library will be honored to present Professor MAX COLEMAN,
                Senior Research Scientist from NASA/Cal Tech with a lecture on how the agency is searching for life on
                other planets.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pharmaceutical, Healthcare Leaders Seek Innovation and What’s Next at Critical Event in Europe
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12230839-pharmaceutical-healthcare-leaders-seek-innovation-and-whats-next-at-critical-event-in-europe.html
            </link>
            <description>The Pharma CI Conference &amp; Exhibition continues to be THE INDUSTRY'S GOLD STANDARD for
                senior level pharma, biotech, device, and healthcare professionals seeking the latest news, and the rare
                chance to network with all the industry's luminaries.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>How Will Stem Cell Therapies Impact Patient Care?</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12230607-how-will-stem-cell-therapies-impact-patient-care.html</link>
            <description>Four Action Items Are Key to Success, Says World Stem Cell Report 2013</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Enhancing clinical diagnostics with Tecan’s Cavro® Omni Robot</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12230506-enhancing-clinical-diagnostics-with-tecans-cavro-omni-robot.html</link>
            <description>Zivak Technologies, based in Istanbul, Turkey, relies on Tecan’s Cavro® Omni Robot to automate
                liquid handling for its clinical diagnostic HPLC and LC­MSMS systems.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cepheid’s next generation Xpert® Flu test receives European CE IVD clearance</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12230502-cepheids-next-generation-xpert-flu-test-receives-european-ce-ivd-clearance.html
            </link>
            <description>Cepheid is pleased to announce the launch of its next generation Xpert Flu test for the
                GeneXpert® System, a CE IVD marked product offering on-demand STAT testing for triage, outbreaks,
                emergencies and high risk patient management.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Pharmaceutical Experts Examine Critical Issues, Innovative Ideas at ‘Super Bowl&quot; of Pharma
                Events
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12229950-pharmaceutical-experts-examine-critical-issues-innovative-ideas-at-super-bowl-of-pharma-events.html
            </link>
            <description>There's a reason why 300+ people attended last year. The Pharma Market Research Conference
                brings together the industry's clear leaders in a unique setting that promotes innovative thinking and
                meaningful networking.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Akermin, Inc. Receives $3 Million Cooperative Agreement from the U.S. Department of Energy</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12229427-akermin-inc-receives-3-million-cooperative-agreement-from-the-us-department-of-energy.html
            </link>
            <description>Research will support development of the technology for post-combustion CO2 removal from power
                plants
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Organomation Announces Laboratory Evaporator Article Series</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12229337-organomation-announces-laboratory-evaporator-article-series.html</link>
            <description>This fall, Organomation will publish several laboratory evaporator themed pieces to the
                company's blog. They will focus on critical topics including optimum operating conditions for laboratory
                evaporators and preventing sample contamination.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Global Media Strategies to Attend Biotech Roundtable October 25</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12228354-global-media-strategies-to-attend-biotech-roundtable-october-25.html
            </link>
            <description>Event is Latest in String of Life Sciences, Technology Industry Participatory Efforts
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>IMCD Group opens its first pharmaceutical laboratory</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12228083-imcd-group-opens-its-first-pharmaceutical-laboratory.html</link>
            <description>IMCD Group, a leading speciality chemicals distributor, has significantly expanded its
                laboratory capability with the addition of a new pharmaceutical laboratory in Huerth (near Cologne),
                Germany.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SHL to Inspire Innovation at the 2013 PDA Conference in Basel, Switzerland</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12228076-shl-to-inspire-innovation-at-the-2013-pda-conference-in-basel-switzerland.html
            </link>
            <description>SHL will be exhibiting at our Innovation Bar at Booth #64 at PDA’s 2013 - The Universe of
                Pre-filled Syringes &amp; Injection Devices in Basel, Switzerland
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Zenalux Adds Pressure Sensing Capability to Zenascope™ System</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12227052-zenalux-adds-pressure-sensing-capability-to-zenascope-system.html</link>
            <description>Pressure reading function allows users to dial in target pressure via user interface…
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Innovation Oktoberfest! Of emerging Biotech Stars and sleepy Angels!</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226867-innovation-oktoberfest-of-emerging-biotech-stars-and-sleepy-angels.html
            </link>
            <description>The Association of Biotechnology Led Enterprises (ABLE) conducted its’ 5th edition of
                Biotechnology Entrepreneurship Student Team (BEST) event, in collaboration with the Department of
                Biotechnology in Bangalore from October 9th to 13th.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BioVision introduces DiaEasy™ Dialyzer tubes - the most user friendly dialysis sets on the market.
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226680-biovision-introduces-diaeasy-dialyzer-tubes-the-most-user-friendly-dialysis-sets-on-the-market.html
            </link>
            <description>Biovision is very excited to introduce the DiaEasy™ Dialyzer tubes product line in our protein
                extraction and purification portfolio.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Good news for drug delivery researchers: AbboMax offers a portfolio of liposome reagents</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12226498-good-news-for-drug-delivery-researchers-abbomax-offers-portfolio-of-liposome-reagents.html
            </link>
            <description>Liposomes are artificially-prepared vesicles that are made out of the same material as a cell
                membrane, a lipid bilayer, used as vehicles for drug delivery. AbboMax offers innovative liposome
                reagents with a large number of lipid compositions.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Probiotic GanedenBC30 approved by Venezuelan Popular Power Ministry of Health for Food Application
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225834-probiotic-ganedenbc30-approved-by-venezuelan-popular-power-ministry-of-health-for-food-application.html
            </link>
            <description>Exclusive Distribution by Biotecnologia 3000 C.A. Will Generate Innovative Foods &amp;
                Beverages
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BioVision launches the first edition of the &quot;EPIGENETICS RESEARCH TOOLS&quot; brochure</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225818-biovision-launches-the-first-edition-of-the-epigenetics-research-tools-brochure.html
            </link>
            <description>BioVision is very excited to announce the launch of the first edition of this latest brochure
                titled: “Epigenetics Research Tools”.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>BPS Bioscience, Inc. Announces HCV profiling Service and New Tools for HCV Research</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225809-bps-bioscience-inc-announces-hcv-profiling-service-and-new-tools-for-hcv-research.html
            </link>
            <description>BPS Bioscience, Inc. (“BPS”) announces the addition of a panel of 6 protease enzymes for
                identifying small molecule inhibitors of the Hepatitis C virus (HCV). These unique enzymes are also
                available for custom screening and profiling services.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>MedImpact-Onco360 Collaboration Addresses Unique Needs of Cancer Care</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12225024-medimpact-onco360-collaboration-addresses-unique-needs-of-cancer-care.html
            </link>
            <description>MedImpact Healthcare Systems, Inc., the nation’s largest privately held provider of pharmacy
                benefit management (PBM) services, and Onco360, the fastest-growing independent Oncology Pharmacy and
                Clinical Support Services company, today announced a...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New Technology &quot;right under our nose&quot; - Assurance Alar One-Sense highlighted at annual ASA
                meeting
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12224436-new-technology-right-under-our-nose-assurance-alar-one-sense-highlighted-at-annual-asa-meeting.html
            </link>
            <description>Assurance® Alar One-Sense™ Pulse Oximetry Sensor Highlighted in Three Clinical Presentations at
                American Society of Anesthesiologists Annual Meeting A New Technology “Right Under Our Nose” –
                Highlights Benefits of Pulse Oximetry Monitoring at...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Cambridge Healthtech Institute Announces Molecular Med Tri-Conference 2014 Short Courses</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12223572-cambridge-healthtech-institute-announces-molecular-med-tri-conference-2014-short-courses.html
            </link>
            <description>Twenty 3-hour short courses to be held at the 21st International Tri-Conference.</description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Tecan Academy launched in Europe</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12223320-tecan-academy-launched-in-europe.html</link>
            <description>Tecan is pleased to announce the European launch of its Tecan Academy web-based training
                tool.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>New England Biolabs® Sponsors Upcoming Masquerade Benefit for ArtCorps®</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12221148-new-england-biolabs-sponsors-upcoming-masquerade-benefit-for-artcorps.html
            </link>
            <description>To celebrate and support ArtCorps' Creative Leadership for Social Change programs, New England
                Biolabs, Inc. (NEB®) is sponsoring Raising Spirits: A Masquerade Benefit for ArtCorps®, which will take
                place on October 24, 2013 in Ipswich, MA.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Enhanced betatrophin and type 1 diabetes research via sample preparation reagent AlbuVoid™</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12221686-enhanced-betatrophin-and-type-1-diabetes-research-via-sample-preparation-reagent-albuvoid.html
            </link>
            <description>The article titled, “Increased circulating levels of betatrophin in individuals with
                long-standing type 1 diabetes” utilized AlbuVoid™’s albumin depletion protocol for removing albumin from
                plasma samples
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>ReproTech Founder Receives American Association of Tissue Banks Award</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12219944-reprotech-founder-receives-american-association-of-tissue-banks-award.html
            </link>
            <description>The American Association of Tissue Banks recognized Russell Bierbaum, ReproTech, Ltd. founder
                and former President, for his contributions to the tissue banking industry this week at its annual
                meeting.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>RespInnovation Launch RespIn 11 Bronchial Clearance System - A New Generation of HFCWO Therapy
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12221000-respinnovation-launch-respin-11-bronchial-clearance-system-new-generation-of-hfcwo-therapy.html
            </link>
            <description>RespInnovation has been awarded ISO 9001 and ISO 13485 certification and granted US Food and
                Drug Administration (US FDA) accreditation and now CE accreditation.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SalutarisMD Wet AMD Treatment - Long Term Positive Outcomes Presented at Ophthalmology Futures
                Forum
            </title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12218705-salutarismd-wet-amd-treatment-long-term-positive-outcomes-presented-at-ophthalmology-futures-forum.html
            </link>
            <description>At the Ophthalmology Futures European Forum yesterday, results were presented from a cohort
                study evaluating the use of a minimally invasive retrobulbar episcleral brachytherapy device developed
                by Salutaris Medical Devices, Ltd.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Dow AgroSciences and Synpromics Announce R&amp;D Collaboration</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12220424-dow-agrosciences-and-synpromics-announce-rd-collaboration.html</link>
            <description>INDIANAPOLIS AND EDINBURGH, SCOTLAND - (OCT. 3, 2013) - Synpromics, the synthetic promoter
                company, announces an important collaboration with Dow AgroSciences, a wholly owned subsidiary of The
                Dow Chemical Company (NYSE: DOW), to develop Synpromics’...
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Today's NEWS,Elon Musk is talking with the CEO of KC &amp; MADISON PHILLIPS,Wind Energy &quot;Pioneers&quot;.</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12220330-todays-newselon-musk-is-talking-with-the-ceo-of-kc-madison-phillipswind-energy-pioneers.html
            </link>
            <description>KC &amp; MADISON PHILLIPS is a Wind Energy Innovator,they are together with the Inventor of
                this New Wind Technology,what is Originated from a European Inventor,His name will be announce when the
                Deal will be Closed by both Company.
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>Looking for the next generation in microfluidics</title>
            <link>http://www.prlog.org/12219932-looking-for-the-next-generation-in-microfluidics.html</link>
            <description>Dolomite’s Productizing Science® Competition 2013 offers scientists a chance to turn
                microfluidic innovations into successful products
            </description>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title>SHL GM Frank Isaksson signs second LOI to further increase investments in Taiwan</title>
            <link>
                http://www.prlog.org/12219757-shl-gm-frank-isaksson-signs-second-loi-to-further-increase-investments-in-taiwan.html
            </link>
            <description>SHL Group signed a second Letter of Intent with the Taiwan Ministry of Economic Affairs to
                invest an additional $40 million USD in Taiwan.
            </description>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>